{
    "subject": "Nasser_Taghvai",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Captain_Khorshid",
    "human_readable": "Nasser Taghvai created Captain Khorshid.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9864534735679626,
            "question": "Is Nasser Taghvai known for creating Captain Khorshid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8653374314308167,
            "question": "Who created Captain Khorshid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.831728458404541,
            "question": "Who is the creator of Captain Khorshid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7853763103485107,
            "question": "What did Nasser Taghvai create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7425511479377747,
            "question": "What is the name of the character created by Nasser Taghvai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.582110583782196,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Captain Khorshid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49529528617858887,
            "question": "What type of work is Captain Khorshid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49231475591659546,
            "question": "Is Captain Khorshid a fictional character?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4856182336807251,
            "question": "What is the story behind Captain Khorshid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46782639622688293,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of Captain Khorshid?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nasser Taghvai created Captain Khorshid.",
            "html": "yago_10652_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the story behind Captain Khorshid?",
            "html": "yago_10652_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Captain Khorshid a fictional character?",
            "html": "yago_10652_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work is Captain Khorshid?",
            "html": "yago_10652_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10652_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10652_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10652_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10652_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10652_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10652_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10652_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10652_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10652_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10652_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Nasser Taghvai directed and made the film \"Captain Khorshid\" (e.g. file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_10652/re-ranker-msmarco/58.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_10652/re-ranker-msmarco/87.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Nasser Taghvai created Captain Khorshid.\" Specifically, multiple documents mention Nasser Taghvai as the director of the film 'Captain Khorshid', which indicates he was involved in creating it."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}